Never give up hope.
The Hill is a history, drama film directed by Jeff Celentano.
The story of Rickey Hill, who overcomes his physical disability and repairs his relationship
with his father in a quest to become a major league baseball (MLB) player.
Rickey Hill, played by Colin Ford.
James Hill, played by Dennis Quaid.
Helen Hill, played by Joelle Carter.
Red Murff, played by Scott Glenn.
Gracie Shanz, played by Siena Bjornerud.
Robert Hill, played by Ryan Dinning.
The Hill is a 2023 American biographical sports drama film about baseball player Rickey Hill
overcoming a physical handicap in order to try out for a legendary major league scout.
It was directed by Jeff Celentano from a screenplay by
Angelo Pizzo and Scott Marshall Smith.
It stars Dennis Quaid, Colin Ford, Joelle Carter, Randy Houser,
Jesse Berry, Bonnie Bedelia, and Scott Glenn.
The film was released in the United States in theaters by
Briarcliff Entertainment on August 25, 2023.
The film explores themes of baseball, based on true story, christian faith.
The tone is emotional.